...because she's afraid
she's not smart enough for Leonard.
(Leonard:)So it's nothing I did? It's her problem?
(Sheldon:)I drank milk that tasted funny.
(Leonard:)Penny thinks I'm too smart for her.
That's ridiculous.
(Penny:)I know.
(Sheldon:)Most of your work is extremely derivative.
And don't worry, that's not a secret.
(Sheldon:)Everybody knows.
(Howard:)- Hi.
- Yeah, hi. Listen.
(Leonard:)I know what's been bothering you about us,
and I have the answer.
- What are you talking about?
- I wanna say that it's not Sheldon's fault.
(Leonard:)He tried very hard to keep your secret.
(Leonard:)If Howard hadn't drugged him,
he would've taken it to his grave.
- He told you?
- Yes, but it's okay.
(Leonard:)Now that we know what the problem is,
there's a simple solution.